

MEDINA NURAINSY

My career as a project administrator staff began when I started working for Specialised Plumbing and Drainage who cooperate with PT Total Cipta Persada in Surabaya. I have administered numerous projects, creating and reviewing budgets, estimating prices, and purchasing orders of products for clients. Also I'm dedicated, meticulous, and organized person.

EDUCATION

University Of Muhammadiyah Malang 2013 - 2018 | English Education

SMAN 1 Sampit

2009 - 2012

SKILLS

- Planswift
- Corel Draw
- Drawing
- Simpro

CONTACT

medina.nurainsy@gmail.com

+6285393924488

Jl.Pinang 4 No.40 Sampit, Kalimantan Tengah, Indonesia

EXPERIENCE

January 2019 - May 2020

Specialised Plumbing & Drainage Admin Project and Estimator

- Performed general clerical duties, such as data entry, mailing client, and filing price of product.
- Scheduling daily activity for construction workers
- Reviewing and evaluating cost of project such as roof installation of client.
- Analyze drawings and specifications to ensure that the entire scope of work is understood and has been addressed to the client
- Creating a budget for clients using estimating software for demolition and roof construction projects.
- Creating new project estimates and enter the data into estimate software, writing of sub-contractor scopes of work and preparation of change order documentation.

Sept. 2016 - Sept. 2017

University Of Muhammadiyah Malang Administration Employee (Part Timer)

- Entry data and operate the computer and filing.
- Assist the lecturers' project.

January 2015 - December 2017

University Of Muhammadiyah Malang Journalist and Layouter of Campus Newspaper

- Headed the layout team and design the rubrics of Bestari newspaper.
- As a journalist and write news.
- Illustrate the news from some rubrics.